[{"question":"1. What is the purpose of the OSI physical layer?","answers":[{"text":"controlling access to media","isCorrect":false},{"text":"transmitting bits across the local media","isCorrect":true},{"text":"performing error detection on received frames","isCorrect":false},{"text":"exchanging frames between nodes over physical network media","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"2. Why are two strands of fiber used for a single fiber optic connection?","answers":[{"text":"The two strands allow the data to travel for longer distances without degrading.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They prevent crosstalk from causing interference on the connection.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They increase the speed at which the data can travel.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They allow for full-duplex connectivity.","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"3. Which characteristic describes crosstalk?","answers":[{"text":"the distortion of the network signal from fluorescent lighting","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the distortion of the transmitted messages from signals carried in adjacent wires","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the weakening of the network signal over long cable lengths","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the loss of wireless signal over excessive distance from the access point","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"4. Which procedure is used to reduce the effect of crosstalk in copper cables?","answers":[{"text":"requiring proper grounding connections","isCorrect":false},{"text":"twisting opposing circuit wire pairs together","isCorrect":true},{"text":"wrapping the bundle of wires with metallic shielding","isCorrect":false},{"text":"designing a cable infrastructure to avoid crosstalk interference","isCorrect":false},{"text":"avoiding sharp bends during installation","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"6. A network administrator is measuring the transfer of bits across the company backbone for a mission critical financial application. The administrator notices that the network throughput appears lower than the bandwidth expected. Which three factors could influence the differences in throughput? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"the amount of traffic that is currently crossing the network","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the sophistication of the encapsulation method applied to the data","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the type of traffic that is crossing the network","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the latency that is created by the number of network devices that the data is crossing","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the bandwidth of the WAN connection to the Internet","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the reliability of the gigabit Ethernet infrastructure of the backbone","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"9. With the use of unshielded twisted-pair copper wire in a network, what causes crosstalk within the cable pairs?","answers":[{"text":"the magnetic field around the adjacent pairs of wire","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the use of braided wire to shield the adjacent wire pairs","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the reflection of the electrical wave back from the far end of the cable","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the collision caused by two nodes trying to use the media simultaneously","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"10. Refer to the graphic. What type of cabling is shown?","answers":[{"text":"STP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UTP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"coax","isCorrect":false},{"text":"fiber","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"UTP cable consists of four pairs of color-coded wires that have been twisted together and then encased in a flexible plastic sheath.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"STP cable uses four pairs of wires, each wrapped in a foil shield, which are then wrapped in an overall metallic braid or foil.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Coaxial cable uses a copper conductor and a layer of flexible plastic insulation surrounds the copper conductor.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Fiber cable is a flexible, extremely thin, transparent strand of glass surrounded by plastic insulation.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"11. In addition to the cable length, what two factors could interfere with the communication carried over UTP cables? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"crosstalk","isCorrect":true},{"text":"bandwidth","isCorrect":false},{"text":"size of the network","isCorrect":false},{"text":"signal modulation technique","isCorrect":false},{"text":"electromagnetic interference","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"Electromagnetic interference (EMI) or radio frequency interference (RFI) – EMI and RFI signals can distort and corrupt the data signals being carried by copper media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Crosstalk – Crosstalk is a disturbance caused by the electric or magnetic fields of a signal on one wire interfering with the signal in an adjacent wire.","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"12. Refer to the graphic. What type of cabling is shown?","answers":[{"text":"STP","isCorrect":false},{"text":"UTP","isCorrect":true},{"text":"coax","isCorrect":false},{"text":"fiber","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"13. Which two devices commonly affect wireless networks? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Blu-ray players","isCorrect":false},{"text":"home theaters","isCorrect":false},{"text":"cordless phones","isCorrect":true},{"text":"microwaves","isCorrect":true},{"text":"incandescent light bulbs","isCorrect":false},{"text":"external hard drives","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"14. Which two statements describe the services provided by the data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"It defines the end-to-end delivery addressing scheme.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It maintains the path between the source and destination devices during the data transmission.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It manages the access of frames to the network media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"It provides reliable delivery through link establishment and flow control.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It ensures that application data will be transmitted according to the prioritization.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It packages various Layer 3 PDUs into a frame format that is compatible with the network interface.","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"15. What is the function of the CRC value that is found in the FCS field of a frame?","answers":[{"text":"to verify the integrity of the received frame","isCorrect":true},{"text":"to verify the physical address in the frame","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to verify the logical address in the frame","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to compute the checksum header for the data field in the frame","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"16. What is contained in the trailer of a data-link frame?","answers":[{"text":"logical address","isCorrect":false},{"text":"physical address","isCorrect":false},{"text":"data","isCorrect":false},{"text":"error detection","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"17. Which statement describes a characteristic of the frame header fields of the data link layer?","answers":[{"text":"They all include the flow control and logical connection fields.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Ethernet frame header fields contain Layer 3 source and destination addresses.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"They vary depending on protocols.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"They include information on user applications.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"18. A network team is comparing physical WAN topologies for connecting remote sites to a headquarters building. Which topology provides high availability and connects some, but not all, remote sites?","answers":[{"text":"mesh","isCorrect":false},{"text":"partial mesh","isCorrect":true},{"text":"hub and spoke","isCorrect":false},{"text":"point-to-point","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"19. Which two fields or features does Ethernet examine to determine if a received frame is passed to the data link layer or discarded by the NIC? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"auto-MDIX","isCorrect":false},{"text":"CEF","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Frame Check Sequence","isCorrect":true},{"text":"minimum frame size","isCorrect":true},{"text":"source MAC address","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"20. Which media communication type does not require media arbitration in the data link layer?","answers":[{"text":"deterministic","isCorrect":false},{"text":"half-duplex","isCorrect":false},{"text":"full-duplex","isCorrect":true},{"text":"controlled access","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"21. Which statement describes an extended star topology?","answers":[{"text":"End devices connect to a central intermediate device, which in turn connects to other central intermediate devices.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"End devices are connected together by a bus and each bus connects to a central intermediate device.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Each end system is connected to its respective neighbor via an intermediate device.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"All end and intermediate devices are connected in a chain to each other.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"22. What is a characteristic of the LLC sublayer?","answers":[{"text":"It provides the logical addressing required that identifies the device.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It provides delimitation of data according to the physical signaling requirements of the medium.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It places information in the frame allowing multiple Layer 3 protocols to use the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"It defines software processes that provide services to the physical layer.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"23. What are three ways that media access control is used in networking? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"Ethernet utilizes CSMA/CD.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Media access control provides placement of data frames onto the media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Contention-based access is also known as deterministic.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"802.11 utilizes CSMA/CD.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Data link layer protocols define the rules for access to different media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Networks with controlled access have reduced performance due to data collisions.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"24. During the encapsulation process, what occurs at the data link layer for a PC connected to an Ethernet network?","answers":[{"text":"An IP address is added.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The logical address is added.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The physical address is added.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The process port number is added.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"25. What three items are contained in an Ethernet header and trailer? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"source IP address","isCorrect":false},{"text":"source MAC address","isCorrect":true},{"text":"destination IP address","isCorrect":false},{"text":"destination MAC address","isCorrect":true},{"text":"error-checking information","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"Frame start and stop indicator flags at the beginning and end of a frame","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Addressing – for Ethernet networks this part of the header contains source and destination MAC addresses","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Type field to indicate what Layer 3 protocol is being used","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Error detection to determine if the frame arrived without error","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"26. What type of communication rule would best describe CSMA/CD?","answers":[{"text":"access method","isCorrect":true},{"text":"flow control","isCorrect":false},{"text":"message encapsulation","isCorrect":false},{"text":"message encoding","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"27. Which three basic parts are common to all frame types supported by the data link layer? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"header","isCorrect":true},{"text":"type field","isCorrect":false},{"text":"MTU size","isCorrect":false},{"text":"data","isCorrect":true},{"text":"trailer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"CRC value","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"Header","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Data","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Trailer","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"28. Which statement is true about the CSMA/CD access method that is used in Ethernet?","answers":[{"text":"When a device hears a carrier signal and transmits, a collision cannot occur.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"A jamming signal causes only devices that caused the collision to execute a backoff algorithm.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"All network devices must listen before transmitting.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Devices involved in a collision get priority to transmit after the backoff period.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"29. What is the auto-MDIX feature on a switch?","answers":[{"text":"the automatic configuration of an interface for 10/100/1000 Mb/s operation","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the automatic configuration of an interface for a straight-through or a crossover Ethernet cable connection","isCorrect":true},{"text":"the automatic configuration of full-duplex operation over a single Ethernet copper or optical cable","isCorrect":false},{"text":"the ability to turn a switch interface on or off accordingly if an active connection is detected","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"31. A Layer 2 switch is used to switch incoming frames from a 1000BASE-T port to a port connected to a 100Base-T network. Which method of memory buffering would work best for this task?","answers":[{"text":"port-based buffering","isCorrect":false},{"text":"level 1 cache buffering","isCorrect":false},{"text":"shared memory buffering","isCorrect":true},{"text":"fixed configuration buffering","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"34. What is the purpose of the FCS field in a frame?","answers":[{"text":"to obtain the MAC address of the sending node","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to verify the logical address of the sending node","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to compute the CRC header for the data field","isCorrect":false},{"text":"to determine if errors occurred in the transmission and reception","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"35. Which switching method has the lowest level of latency?","answers":[{"text":"cut-through","isCorrect":false},{"text":"store-and-forward","isCorrect":false},{"text":"fragment-free","isCorrect":false},{"text":"fast-forward","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"36. A network administrator is connecting two modern switches using a straight-through cable. The switches are new and have never been configured. Which three statements are correct about the final result of the connection? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"The link between the switches will work at the fastest speed that is supported by both switches.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The link between switches will work as full-duplex.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"If both switches support different speeds, they will each work at their own fastest speed.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The auto-MDIX feature will configure the interfaces eliminating the need for a crossover cable.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The connection will not be possible unless the administrator changes the cable to a crossover cable.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The duplex capability has to be manually configured because it cannot be negotiated.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"37. Which advantage does the store-and-forward switching method have compared with the cut-through switching method?","answers":[{"text":"collision detecting","isCorrect":false},{"text":"frame error checking","isCorrect":true},{"text":"faster frame forwarding","isCorrect":false},{"text":"frame forwarding using IPv4 Layer 3 and 4 information","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"38. When the store-and-forward method of switching is in use, what part of the Ethernet frame is used to perform an error check?","answers":[{"text":"CRC in the trailer","isCorrect":true},{"text":"source MAC address in the header","isCorrect":false},{"text":"destination MAC address in the header","isCorrect":false},{"text":"protocol type in the header","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"40. What are two actions performed by a Cisco switch? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"building a routing table that is based on the first IP address in the frame header","isCorrect":false},{"text":"using the source MAC addresses of frames to build and maintain a MAC address table","isCorrect":true},{"text":"forwarding frames with unknown destination IP addresses to the default gateway","isCorrect":false},{"text":"utilizing the MAC address table to forward frames via the destination MAC address","isCorrect":true},{"text":"examining the destination MAC address to add new entries to the MAC address table","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Explanation:","answers":[{"text":"When a frame comes in, the switch examines the Layer 2 source address to build and maintain the Layer 2 MAC address table.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It examines the Layer 2 destination address to determine how to forward the frame. When the destination address is in the MAC address table, then the frame is sent out a particular port. When the address is unknown, the frame is sent to all ports that have devices connected to that network.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"41. Which two statements describe features or functions of the logical link control sublayer in Ethernet standards? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Logical link control is implemented in software.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Logical link control is specified in the IEEE 802.3 standard.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The LLC sublayer adds a header and a trailer to the data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The data link layer uses LLC to communicate with the upper layers of the protocol suite.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The LLC sublayer is responsible for the placement and retrieval of frames on and off the media.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"42. What is the auto-MDIX feature?","answers":[{"text":"It enables a device to automatically configure an interface to use a straight-through or a crossover cable.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"It enables a device to automatically configure the duplex settings of a segment.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It enables a device to automatically configure the speed of its interface.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"It enables a switch to dynamically select the forwarding method.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"44. Which is a multicast MAC address?","answers":[{"text":"FF-FF-FF-FF-FF-FF","isCorrect":false},{"text":"5C-26-0A-4B-19-3E","isCorrect":false},{"text":"01-00-5E-00-00-03","isCorrect":true},{"text":"00-26-0F-4B-00-3E","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"48. What does the term “attenuation” mean in data communication?","answers":[{"text":"loss of signal strength as distance increases","isCorrect":true},{"text":"time for a signal to reach its destination","isCorrect":false},{"text":"leakage of signals from one cable pair to another","isCorrect":false},{"text":"strengthening of a signal by a networking device","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"49. What makes fiber preferable to copper cabling for interconnecting buildings? (Choose three.)","answers":[{"text":"greater distances per cable run","isCorrect":true},{"text":"lower installation cost","isCorrect":false},{"text":"limited susceptibility to EMI/RFI","isCorrect":true},{"text":"durable connections","isCorrect":false},{"text":"greater bandwidth potential","isCorrect":true},{"text":"easily terminated","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"50. What OSI physical layer term describes the process by which one wave modifies another wave?","answers":[{"text":"modulation","isCorrect":true},{"text":"IEEE","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EIA/TIA","isCorrect":false},{"text":"air","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"51. What OSI physical layer term describes the capacity at which a medium can carry data?","answers":[{"text":"bandwidth","isCorrect":true},{"text":"IEEE","isCorrect":false},{"text":"EIA/TIA","isCorrect":false},{"text":"air","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"53. What OSI physical layer term describes the measure of the transfer of bits across a medium over a given period of time?","answers":[{"text":"throughput","isCorrect":true},{"text":"bandwidth","isCorrect":false},{"text":"latency","isCorrect":false},{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"54. What OSI physical layer term describes the amount of time, including delays, for data to travel from one point to another?","answers":[{"text":"latency","isCorrect":true},{"text":"bandwidth","isCorrect":false},{"text":"throughput","isCorrect":false},{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"55. What OSI physical layer term describes the amount of time, including delays, for data to travel from one point to another?","answers":[{"text":"latency","isCorrect":true},{"text":"fiber-optic cable","isCorrect":false},{"text":"air","isCorrect":false},{"text":"copper cable","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"56. What OSI physical layer term describes the measure of usable data transferred over a given period of time?","answers":[{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":true},{"text":"fiber-optic cable","isCorrect":false},{"text":"air","isCorrect":false},{"text":"copper cable","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"57. What OSI physical layer term describes the physical medium which uses electrical pulses?","answers":[{"text":"copper cable","isCorrect":true},{"text":"fiber-optic cable","isCorrect":false},{"text":"air","isCorrect":false},{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"58. What OSI physical layer term describes the physical medium that uses the propagation of light?","answers":[{"text":"fiber-optic cable","isCorrect":true},{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":false},{"text":"latency","isCorrect":false},{"text":"throughput","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"59. What OSI physical layer term describes the physical medium for microwave transmissions?","answers":[{"text":"air","isCorrect":true},{"text":"goodput","isCorrect":false},{"text":"latency","isCorrect":false},{"text":"throughput","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"60. Which two functions are performed at the MAC sublayer of the OSI data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Places information in the frame that identifies which network layer protocol is being used for the frame.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Controls the NIC responsible for sending and receiving data on the physical medium.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Implements a trailer to detect transmission errors.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Case 2:","answers":[{"text":"Provides synchronization between source and target nodes.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Communicates between the networking software at the upper layers and the device hardware at the lower layers.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Case 3:","answers":[{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Provides synchronization between source and target nodes.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Implements a trailer to detect transmission errors.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Places information in the frame that identifies which network layer protocol is being used for the frame.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Case 4:","answers":[{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Communicates between the networking software at the upper layers and the device hardware at the lower layers.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Provides synchronization between source and target nodes.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Case 5:","answers":[{"text":"Places information in the frame that identifies which network layer protocol is being used for the frame.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Controls the NIC responsible for sending and receiving data on the physical medium.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Communicates between the networking software at the upper layers and the device hardware at the lower layers.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"Case 6:","answers":[{"text":"Controls the NIC responsible for sending and receiving data on the physical medium","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Provides a mechanism to allow multiple devices to communicate over a shared medium.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"61. Which two functions are performed at the LLC sublayer of the OSI data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Places information in the frame that identifies which network layer protocol is being used for the frame.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Implements a process to delimit fields within a Layer 2 frame.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Controls the NIC responsible for sending and receiving data on the physical medium.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"64. Which two functions are performed at the LLC sublayer of the OSI data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Places information in the frame that identifies which network layer protocol is being used for the frame.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Performs data encapsulation.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Controls the NIC responsible for sending and receiving data on the physical medium.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"66. Which two functions are performed at the LLC sublayer of the OSI data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Provides data link layer addressing.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Implements a trailer to detect transmission errors.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Provides synchronization between source and target nodes.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"68. Which two functions are performed at the LLC sublayer of the OSI data link layer? (Choose two.)","answers":[{"text":"Enables IPv4 and IPv6 to utilize the same network interface and media.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Adds Layer 2 control information to network protocol data.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"Integrates various physical technologies.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Implements a trailer to detect transmission errors.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"Provides synchronization between source and target nodes.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"71. What action will occur if a switch receives a frame with the destination MAC address FF:FF:FF:FF:FF:FF?","answers":[{"text":"The switch forwards it out all ports except the ingress port.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The switch shares the MAC address table entry with any connected switches.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch does not forward the frame.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch sends the frame to a connected router because the destination MAC address is not local.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"73. What action will occur if a switch receives a frame with the destination MAC address 01:00:5E:00:00:D9?","answers":[{"text":"The switch forwards it out all ports except the ingress port.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The switch does not forward the frame.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch sends the frame to a connected router because the destination MAC address is not local.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch shares the MAC address table entry with any connected switches.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"74. What action will occur if a host receives a frame with a destination MAC address of FF:FF:FF:FF:FF:FF?","answers":[{"text":"The host will process the frame.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The host forwards the frame to the router.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host sends the frame to the switch to update the MAC address table.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host forwards the frame to all other hosts.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"75. What action will occur if a switch receives a frame and does have the source MAC address in the MAC table?","answers":[{"text":"The switch refreshes the timer on that entry.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The switch adds it to its MAC address table associated with the port number.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch forwards the frame to the associated port.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The switch sends the frame to a connected router because the destination MAC address is not local.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"76. What action will occur if a host receives a frame with a destination MAC address of FF:FF:FF:FF:FF:FF?","answers":[{"text":"The host will process the frame.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The host returns the frame to the switch.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host replies to the switch with its own IP address.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host forwards the frame to all other hosts.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"78. What action will occur if a host receives a frame with a destination MAC address it does not recognize?","answers":[{"text":"The host will discard the frame.","isCorrect":true},{"text":"The host replies to the switch with its own IP address.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host forwards the frame to all other hosts.","isCorrect":false},{"text":"The host returns the frame to the switch.","isCorrect":false}]},{"question":"79. Which type of UTP cable is used to connect a PC to a switch port?","answers":[{"text":"console","isCorrect":false},{"text":"rollover","isCorrect":false},{"text":"crossover","isCorrect":false},{"text":"straight-through","isCorrect":true}]},{"question":"80. Which type of UTP cable is used to connect a PC to a switch port?","answers":[{"text":"console","isCorrect":false},{"text":"rollover","isCorrect":false},{"text":"crossover","isCorrect":false},{"text":"straight-through","isCorrect":true},{"text":"","isCorrect":false}]}]